var questions = [
  {
    "question":
        "Which consensus mechanism does Bitcoin use to secure its network?",
    "answers": [
      "Proof of Stake (PoS)",
      "Proof of Work (PoW)",
      "Delegated Proof of Stake (DPoS)",
      "Proof of Authority (PoA)",
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "What key aspect helps Layer 1 networks support decentralized applications?",
    "answers": [
      "Centralized control",
      "Their foundational nature as the main blockchain network",
      "The use of fiat currency",
      "Their reliance on third-party institutions",
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1,
  },
  {
    "question":
        "Which stablecoin mechanism uses physical assets to maintain its peg?",
    "answers": [
      "Algorithmic stabilization",
      "Fiat reserves",
      "Proof of Burn",
      "Mining rewards",
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "B",
  },
  {
    "question":
        "What key role do stablecoins play in the cryptocurrency ecosystem?",
    "answers": [
      "Enabling easy fiat-to-crypto conversions",
      "Replacing traditional cryptocurrencies",
      "Serving as the foundation for Layer 1 networks",
      "Providing faster transaction speeds for Layer 2 networks",
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "A",
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the primary purpose of Layer 2 networks?",
    "answers": [
      "To improve blockchain scalability and reduce transaction costs",
      "To replace existing Layer 1 networks",
      "To stabilize the value of cryptocurrencies",
      "To implement Proof of Work protocols",
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "A",
  },
  {
    "question":
        "What is a notable feature of the Lightning Network in Bitcoin?",
    "answers": [
      "It helps to burn excess Bitcoin",
      "It provides fiat currency integration",
      "It enables faster transactions with minimal fees",
      "It supports decentralized finance (DeFi) applications",
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "C",
  },
  {
    "question": "What often drives the value of meme coins?",
    "answers": [
      "Network security",
      "Strong fundamentals",
      "Social media hype and community engagement",
      "Regulatory compliance",
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "C",
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of a meme coin?",
    "answers": ["Ethereum", "Dogecoin", "Binance Coin", "Chainlink"],
    "correctAnswer": "B",
  },
  {
    "question": "Which factor is essential when evaluating an AI coin?",
    "answers": [
      "The developer activity and research behind the coin",
      "The total transaction volume of the coin",
      "The meme community supporting the coin",
      "The maximum supply of the coin",
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "A",
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is an example of an AI coin?",
    "answers": ["Solana", "Tether", "Arkham", "Uniswap"],
    "correctAnswer": "C",
  },
];
